Pedro Alexandre Parreira Primor

+351 961241116 | pedro.primor@pm.me | linkedin.com/in/pedroprimor/

ABOUT ME

Computer engineering student with a recently acquired interest in financial technology. Currently enrolled at NOVA SST in Lisbon for the final year of my master's degree. Experience in front-end web development, mobile game development but open to expand my professional expertise to other fields of computer science. Focused on a computer engineering project on the optimization of the logistical challenges of the last-mile delivery step in the postal sector, in collaboration with CTT – Correios de Portugal, S.A..

EDUCATION

NOVA School of Science and TechnologySep. 2017 – PresentIntegrated Master in Computer EngineeringLisbon, PortugalTechnische Universität DresdenApr. 2021 – Oct. 2021Erasmus+ Programme Exchange PeriodDresden, Germany

EXPERIENCE

Front-end Developer and QA Assistant

Jul. 2019 – Aug. 2019

Automatication MJM

Lisbon, Portugal

- Developed React components to display the result of some unit tests on a web page;
- Experimented with AWS Amplify's authentication mechanism;
- Learned to develop unit tests for JavaScript environments using JEST.

Front-end Developer Intern

Apr. 2020 – Jul. 2020

Altitude Software

Lisbon, Portugal

- Developed React components to replace existing ASP.NET components in a contact centers management platform;
- Integrated the components with the application's back-end using C# and ASP.NET.

Projects

Optimization Problems in the Postal Sector | Python, CPLEX

Jan. 2022 – Present

- Operations research and data analytics project;
- Has the main goal of optimizing the last-mile delivery step of the postal distribution process;

My Spelling Game | Unity, C#, SQLite

Jul. 2018 - Nov. 2018

• Developed a 2D mobile game for Android/iOS along with a graphic designer.

EVENTS

Unity Workshop - JORTEC Informática 2019 $Unity, C\#$	Feb. 2019
Android Training Program Android Studio, Java, Kotlin	Nov. 2019
EUROPT Summer School 2022 Mathematical optimization, Game theory	Aug. 2022

LANGUAGES

Proficient: Portuguese, English

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Java, Python, C#, SQL, Cypher, HTML/CSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, Kotlin, Go, Rust

Frameworks: React, Redux, Flutter

Developer tools: Git, webpack, npm, VS Code, Visual Studio, PyCharm, IntelliJ, Eclipse, Android Studio, Unity

Libraries: Material-UI, pandas, NumPy, Matplotlib, scikit-learn, OpenCV

Sofware packages: Tableau, CPLEX